The kettle and the idol
Now that we have our main YouTube project, can I ask you to say the title call in a cute way?
Can I hold your head, Mr. Kettle?
No, not at all. This is the first time I have heard this.
My three main elements.
Thank you very much.
You are the first person to touch my head.
In this corner, you will be introduced to the three elements that make up who you are.
Let's get to know our guest idols better.
Now, please give us your three elements.
Here are my three major elements.
Jalan
1. camera
2. my dog who floats
3. honesty
Next time notice
First one.
I like cameras, and I really like taking pictures.
Is that so?
Yes, I do. I'm also working on a series of articles.
You have a series of articles?
Yes, I am. I like photography.
And by camera, you don't mean a cell phone camera?
No, it's a film camera.
I'm into film cameras, which I've been getting into lately.
And this year, digital cameras are all the rage again.
Digital cameras are in fashion?
Not among you, Mr. Nakayama.
But among the girls of your generation?
Yes. They take movies with digital cameras.
The picture quality is pretty rough, so you can take emo-like pictures.
I see.
And a lot of them uploaded their videos on TikTok.
Maybe that's when it started to become popular again.
That's amazing.
When you came in this morning...
When I met you.
You said you have a camera.
That's right. I recently bought this.
I put it on my shoulder so that I can take pictures anytime I want.
That's right.
I'm walking around.
I used to have a digital camera that gave me better picture quality
But now that I think about it, my cell phone's got better quality.
This one's a little rougher.
Very rough.
Is it really rough?
It's very rough.
But it's a nice touch.
Do you have any interesting pictures
Any interesting pictures?
Recently, this one.
I'm really into movies.
It was made a really long time ago, in 2003.
It's blurry.
It's from 2003.
I can't handle the blurriness or anything.
But I like that.
It picks up all the sounds and stuff.
There's a lot of noise.
But that's also interesting.
Oh my God, I'm taking pictures of the members.
I'm the only one who knows the members.
I'm the only one who knows them.
Backstage.
I spy on them when they're brushing their teeth.
Sneak peeks?
So anyone can take pictures of you being conscious?
You're so cute, you smile and say, "Cheese!
I'd like to take a picture of you stretching without thinking about it.
I'd like to take a picture of her when she's not so self-conscious.
I see.
But I still want to take pictures without confirming it with the person in question.
I'd like you to go as far as putting it out without confirming it with the person in question.
They're going to notice, aren't they?
They look at me like I'm looking at the camera.
I tell them not to worry about it, and I keep taking pictures.
He's taking it, but...
That's not what I'm after.
I don't need that.
If it's too much work, it's too much to hope for.
It's nice to have a good photographer.
Look at me, look at me, look at the camera here.
Look right here at the camera, please.
It's so shiny today.
May I have a wink?
That's a very nice shot.
Nighttime title.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Courtesy of Nicolico.
Thank you very much.